https://www.hitchcock-media.com/privacy-policy.html

Your BasketYour basket is empty.Your AccountLogin / RegisterChange Currency£ GBP (British Pounds)€ EUR (Euro)¥ JPY (Japanese Yen)$ CAD (Canadian Dollars)$ AUD (Australian Dollars)CHF CHF (Swiss Francs)$ MXN (Mexican Peso)Change Language German English (UK) Spanish
$0.00Your BasketYour basket is empty. Added to Basketa2dd637619db145d25705e7800c3bf37 $ USD£ GBP (British Pounds)€ EUR (Euro)¥ JPY (Japanese Yen)$ CAD (Canadian Dollars)$ AUD (Australian Dollars)CHF CHF (Swiss Francs)$ MXN (Mexican Peso) German English (UK) SpanishLogin / RegisterAdvanced SearchPlease enter a search keywordAdvanced SearchPlease enter a search keywordShop by Category Shop by CategoryARTISTSARTISTSAcker BilkA La ModeBig Band Alumni AssnBobby BlandBob GulleyCarmen McRaeChurchillDavid MunyonEric EkstrandThe Four FreshmenGil MachinHarry JamesHarlan SpectorThe Hollywood SquaresIstvan AlapiIzzy ChaitJay PattenJemima Puddle-DuckJoan JonesKameleonKevin GeorgeLes DeMerleMark LlewellynRandy Van HorneRick RayStan KentonStark Naked & The Car ThievesWoody HermanMP3 DownloadsOriginal Live ConcertsAlternativeBluesCountryDanceFolkHolidayInstrumentalInternationalJazzJazzBig Band/SwingContemporary JazzVocal JazzPopRockStandardsGift CardsSale ItemsBackHomePrivacy PolicyCookie SwitchPrivacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy discloses the online privacy practices for www.Hitchcock-Media.com and its affiliates (collectively, "Hitchcock Media") and applies to the information we collect through www.Hitchcock-Media.com (the "Site"). By accessing and/or using the Site, you are consenting to the collection, storage, and disclosure of data as described in this Privacy Policy.Hitchcock Media reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, update, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. We will post any changes to this Policy on this page so you can readily review the most current version. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on the bottom of this Privacy Policy the date it was last updated.Your IP Address An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer every time you browse the Internet. When a user requests a page from the Site, our servers log the user's current IP address. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site.Cookies  The Site is developed using Active Server Pages (ASP), and we use per-session "cookies" (pieces of data your browser stores in your computer's memory at Hitchcock Media's request) to establish user sessions on our server. We use the cookies to carry information about usage from page to page through the Site. Hitchcock Media does not use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to refuse them. If you disable cookies, your browser may experience some erratic behavior on some portions of the Site.Submission Information  When you submit a request for information or ask to receive updates from us, we will ask you to provide a variety of information, including, without limitation, your name, your email address, and the name of your organization.Please Note:  We do not accept proposals concerning film production companies, film/TV scripts or concept papers, themed amusement parks or restaurants.Use of Submission Information  All or any part of the information we collect through the Site (including, without limitation, information regarding funding requests, requests for information or updates, and feedback regarding the Site) is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "Submission Information."As described in our Terms of Use, Hitchcock Media does not accept or collect Submission Information on a confidential or proprietary basis. Consequently, we are free to use Submission Information for any purpose whatsoever.Disclosures to Third Parties  Because Hitchcock Media does not accept or collect Submission Information on a confidential or proprietary basis, from time to time Hitchcock Media may disclose your Submission Information to third parties, including, without limitation, other potential investors, our consultants, our representatives, our affiliated companies and others.Disclosures  For Legal Reasons Hitchcock Media will also disclose Submission Information when it believes, in its sole discretion, that the law requires such disclosure or that such disclosure is necessary to: Comply with the law; Protect and defend the rights or property of Hitchcock Media or others; or Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the public or the users of the Site.Links This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by Hitchcock Media. Other Web sites (including those that we may link to) may have their own policies. Hitchcock Media has no responsibility for or control over the information-collection practices of such third-party Web sites.January 2021Featured ProductDavid Munyon - Dogs Sleeping$11.99 $8.99Best SellersMark Llewellyn - Black Hills Gold$11.99 $8.99Harry James - 32nd Anniversary Night Vol.2$12.99 $9.74Harry James - 32nd Anniversary Night Vol.1$12.99 $9.74On SaleStan Kenton - Clearwater 72$12.99 $9.74Stan Kenton - The Sound of Kenton$12.99 $9.74Woody Herman - Blues In The Night$12.99 $9.74 TopeCommerce by CubeCartWait…Before you go, be sure to sign up to our newsletter for exclusive offers and promotions!Enter your e-mail address to receive our newsletterPlease enter a valid email address.Email address already subscribed. Continue if you wish to unsubscribe.SubscribeUnsubscribe×
